so what's new mark
how is your new job going to be honest i can't complain
i really love the company that i am working for
my coworkers are all really friendly and helpful
they really help me feel welcome
it's a really energetic and fun atmosphere
my boss is hilarious
and he's really flexible
really
how so
he allows me to come in when i want and make my
own hours
i can also leave early if i start early
there is no real dress code either
i can wear jeans and a tee shirt if i want i
can even wear shorts in the summer
wow
it sounds really cool
i can't stand wearing a suit every day
which do you prefer working late or finishing early
i prefer finishing early i really enjoyed the morning
i love getting up early and going for a run their it's
nothing like watching the sunrise well drinking my morning coffee
really
i am opposite
i love sleeping in
i am most alert in the evenings i'm a real night owl
well you know what they say the early bird catches the worm
you know you could be right
maybe i will try to go to bed a little earlier tonight